Guide to the Garden Club of Allegheny County Records, 1913-2012 AIS.2006.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Events, 1914-2009; III.
  - Activities and Events, 1914-2009; 3.
    - Pizzazz Mellon Account and Tax Information, 1983 & 1994 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Pizzazz and Phipps Conservatory (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Pizzazz Photos, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Pizzazz Photos, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Pizzazz Photos and Pamphlets, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Pizzazz PNC Bank Checks and Stubs, 2003-2008 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Pizzazz Press and Pamphlets, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Pizzazz Programs and Pamphlets, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Pizzazz Receipts, 2005-2009 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Pizzazz Reservations, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Pizzazz Sales Tax, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Pizzazz Special Projects Account, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Pizzazz Spring Hat Luncheon, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Pizzazz Treasurer Reports, July 2006-June 2007 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Pizzazz Whirl Magazine, January 2009 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Plant Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Plant Exchange, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Plant Lists (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Portraits of Botanists Exhibition Invitation, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Powder Mill Reserve, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - President's Council, April 26, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Presidents' Workshop, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Presidents' Workshop Manual, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Programs, 1996-1998 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Programs, 2004-2006 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Programs and Projects, 2008-2009 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Questionnaire Returns, November 2003 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Rachel Carson Centennial Celebration, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Rachel Carson Centennial Celebration, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Rachel Carson Homestead Association and Press, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Regent Square Gateway Final Report, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Riverfront Park Designs, 1995-1997 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Riverfront Press (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Riverlife Press (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Riverlife Sponsors (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Rose Garden Project, 1949-1952 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Rose Garden Project, 1956-1960 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Rose Garden Project, 1963-1971 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Rose Garden Project, 1973-1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Rose Garden Project Pictures, Programs and Invitations (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Scholarships, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Scholarships, 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Self-Education Required Reading (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - A Sense of Wonder, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Special Projects, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Spring Garden Valley, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Spring Garden Valley, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Sponsored Events (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Spring Party, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - State and County Air Pollution Hearing, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Step One Conference, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Sewickley Council of Garden Clubs, 1996-1998 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Urban Parks Conference, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Vacation Home Rentals Project, 1989-1999 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Van Engelen Bulb Sale, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Van Engelen Bulb Sale, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Van Engelen Bulb Sale, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Visiting Gardens (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Visiting Gardens Guide (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Visiting Gardens Correspondence, 1949 & 1955 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Visiting Gardens, Mernie Berger Birthday (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Western Pennsylvania Botanical Garden, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Western Pennsylvania Botanical Garden, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - The Wheel of the Seasons Event Description, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Women's Land Army, 1918 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Women's National Farm and Garden Association, 1945-1960 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - YMCA Gardeners, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - YMCA Hazelwood Parklet, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Conservation, 1922-2008; 4.
    The files in this sub-series document the efforts of the GCAC to promote and encourage conservation through various community projects. It also contains information about conservation and environmental awareness.
    - Adopt a School Tree Program Expenses, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Climate Change Information, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Conservation Committee and Volunteers, 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Conservation Community Grants, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Conservation Projects Programs and Pamphlets, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Conservation Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Conservation Reports, 1960-1963 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Earth Partners, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Earth Partners Annual Reports, 1990-1996 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Earth Partners Curriculum for Students (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Earth Partners Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Earth Partners Correspondence and Invitations, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Earth Partners Evaluations Forms and Procedures, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Earth Partners Expenses, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Earth Partners Information and Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Earth Partners Notes, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Earth Partners Order Information and Receipts, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Earth Partners Photos, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Earth Partners Press, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Earth Partners Programs and Photos, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Earth Partners Request for Funds and Budget, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Educational Outreach Programs (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Articles and Pamphlets (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Green Elephant Sale, 1981-1985 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Guffy Hollow Conservation (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Living Green Pamphlet (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Neighborhood Garden Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Scientists on Biodiversity, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Society for Ecological Restoration Annual Conference, November 1997 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Step One Conference, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Student Conservation Association Annual Reports, 1997 & 2007 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Three Rivers Environmental Awards, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Van Engelen Inc. Whole Sale Price List, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - The Volunteer Newsletter, Summer 1998 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Wildflower Conservation Committee Reports, 1922-1930 & 1952-1954 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Horticulture, 1957-2006; 5.
    The horticulture sub-series includes notes and minutes of the Horticulture Committee. It also contains information about events organized by the committee and various other horticultural activities
    - Annual Horticulture Committee Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Annual Horticulture Committee Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Degree in Horticulture, 1971-1974 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Flower Arranging Newsletter, Spring 1998 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Horticultural Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Horticulture Committee, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Horticulture Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Horticulture Committee Events and Schedule, 1989-1992 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Horticulture Minutes, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Horticulture Press and Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Horticulture Projects, 1988-1991 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Horticultural Schedule and Plant Exchanges (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Horticultural Society of Western Pennsylvania Grants, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Interchange Fellowship in Horticulture, 1957-1959 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Invasive Exotic Plants in the Mid-Atlantic, September 1996 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Natural History, January 1996 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Publications, 1914-2009; IV.
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of internal and external publications of the GCAC. These are material printed for, by, and about the GCAC. They include membership directories, by-laws, membership directories and other self-published material. This series is divided into five subseries: Membership Directories, Constitution and By-Laws, History, Bulletins and Newsletters. The material in this series dates from 1914 to 2009.
  - Membership Directories, 1920-2006; 1.
    The subseries consists of the directories and membership lists of the GCAC. All of the directories are from the years of 1914 through 2006 and note positions held by members. The directories also provide a copy of the GCAC's constitution, by-laws, a schedule of the year's meetings, and a list of the club's members and their addresses.
    - Membership Directory, 1920-1921 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Membership Directory, 1922-1923 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Membership Directory, 1929-1930 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Membership Directory, 1933 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Membership Directory, 1936 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Membership Directory, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Membership Directory, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Membership Directory, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Membership Directory, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Membership Directory, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1952-1953 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1957-1958 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Membership Directory [GCA], 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Membership Directory [GCA], 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1995-1996 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED & incomplete], 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 2003-2004 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 2004-2005 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 2005 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Membership Directory [RESTRICTED], 2005-2006 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Constitution and By-laws, 1914-1998; 2.
    The subseries consists of the GCAC's Constitution and By-laws, as well as the by-laws of several other garden clubs. The by-laws included in this subseries come from the GCAC, the GCA, the Pittsburgh Garden Club, and the Sewickley Council of Garden Clubs. The Sewickley Council of Garden Clubs oversees the activities of the diverse garden clubs in the Pittsburgh area. The Pittsburgh Garden Club is another club that is closely affiliated with GCAC and their activities. The GCA by-laws are presented in a small self-published book that also contains various officer and committee reports, a club calendar, and a membership list. Also included is the policy book which was consulted during general meetings to confirm any questions concerning by-laws and voting procedures.
    - GCAC Constitution and By-laws, 1914 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - GCAC Constitution and By-laws, 1918 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - GCAC Constitution and By-laws, 1918 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - GCAC Constitution and By-laws, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - GCAC Constitution and By-laws, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - GCAC Constitution and By-laws, 1991 & 1995 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - GCAC Members, Presidents and By-laws, 1996-1998 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - GCAC Professionalism and By-laws, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Liabilities of Directors and Officers (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Objectives, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Garden Center By-laws, 1962 & 1969 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Policy Book, 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Sewickley Council of Garden Clubs By-laws, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - History, 1914-2008; 3.
    This subseries consists of items that document the history of the GCAC, some of which were produced by the GCA. Such materials provide a context within which the more specific history of the GCAC can be placed. These materials describe projects, record awards, and provide facts about the organization.
    - GCA History, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Twenty-fifth Anniversary History Pamphlet, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Fifty Blooming Years:1913-1963 by Marjorie Gibbon Battles and Catherine Colt Dicky (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Review of Activities Pamphlet, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Seventy-fifth Anniversary Chronicle "Winds of Change", 1963-1988 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Garden Club History, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - History of the GCAC, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - The Past 25 Years History, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - GCAC History Notes, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - History and Current Projects circa 1916 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Seventy-fifth Anniversary History 1914-1989 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - GCAC History of Projects and Gifts, 1914-1999 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Chronological List of Major GCAC Events, 1914-1954 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - History of Committees, 1977-1992 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Five Year History Update, 1999-2003 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - GCAC History Notes for Orientation, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - GCAC History Notes and Purpose, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - History of Projects and Gifts (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Club History and Archives, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - A History of the GCAC (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Archives, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - University of Pittsburgh Archives, 2004-2008 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - The Past Twenty-five Years GCAC History, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Zone V Information, 1981-1985 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - GCA Information Manual, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - GCA Information Manual, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - GCA Information Manual, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - GCA Fact Sheets, 1982-1984 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - GCA Fact Sheet, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - GCA Fact Sheet, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - GCA Fact Sheet, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - GCA Fact Sheet, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - GCA Affiliate Status (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Bulletins, 1936-2009; 4.
    The bulletins in this subseries were published by the GCA and mainly focus on GCA current projects, meetings, and upcoming flower shows.
    - GCA Bulletins, 1936 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - GCA Bulletins, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - GCA Bulletins, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - GCA Bulletins, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - GCA Bulletins, 1995-1997 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - GCA Bulletins, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 5a)
    - GCA Bulletins, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - GCA Bulletins, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - GCA Bulletins, 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - GCA Bulletins, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - GCA Bulletins, 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - GCA Bulletins, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters, 1984-2009; 5.
    This subseries includes club newsletters published by GCAC and feature official GCAC invitations, updates, projects, and events related to the club. Newsletters from other organizations are also included here.
    - GCAC Newsletters, 1988-1994 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - GCAC Newsletters, 1995-2000 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - GCAC Newsletters, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - GCAC Newsletters, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - GCAC Newsletters, 2005-2006 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - GCAC Newsletters, 2007-2009 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters about Birds from Other Organizations, 1984-2006 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters about Gardens from Other Organizations, 2003-2008 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Phipps Newsletters, 2003-2006 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - The Trumpet Vine Newsletter (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1920-2006; V.
  This series contains letters of appreciation from the annual meeting of 1948, letters about activities. The majority of letters include thank you notes and appreciation memos. Other letters include official club activities correspondence and a group of letters received by former GCAC president Mrs. Richardson. The material in this series dates from 1920 to 2006.
  - Correspondence Regarding Meeting Minutes, 1920 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1949 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Regarding the GCA Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Regarding the GCA Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Regarding the GCA Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1959 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Received by Mrs. Frank E. Richardson, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Received by Mrs. Frank E. Richardson, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with GCA, 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Regarding the Annual Conference, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Regarding Zone V, 2004-2006 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence of Lil Fisher, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Ephemera and Media Material, 1914-2005; VI.
  This series is composed of photographs, newspaper clippings, awards and VHS tapes collected by the GCAC. The clippings and photo directly relate to GCAC flower shows, garden exhibits and other GCAC activities. There are also several plaques and ribbons won or given out by the GCAC. There are also ten VHS tapes of the WQED Step One Conference. This series is divided into three subseries. Subseries one is Ephemera Material, subseries two is Step One Conference Media and subseries three is Newspaper Clippings and Scrapbooks. The material in this series dates from 1914 to 2005.
  - Ephemera Material, 1988-2007; 1.
    This subseries contains objects collected and used by the GCAC. There are several medals and ribbons as well as three official GCAC rubber stamps and an ink pad.
    - Official GCAC stamps and stamp pad, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Official GCAC Pocket Seal, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Civic Achievement Award, GCA Amy Montague Medal, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Wooden Photograph of an Unidentified House (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - The Marion Thompson Fuller Brown Conservation Award, May 2, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - First Place Public/Institutional Garden Award Presented to the Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - GCA Award for Club Public Relations Presented to the GCAC, May 12, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Audubon Society Trustee Award Presented to the GCAC, May 23, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Step One Conference Media, 2.
    This subseries contains the WQED video of the Step One Conference on environmental issue.
    - Step One Part 2, 2. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Step One Part 2 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Step One Short Version (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Step One Part 1 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Step One Part 2 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Step One Part 2 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Step One Part 1 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Step One Part 1 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Step One Part 1 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Step One Part 1 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Scrapbooks, 1961-2003; 3.
    This subseries houses oversized materials, newspaper clippings about GCAC flower shows and photographs of gardens and garden exhibits. The newspaper clippings, all from local Pittsburgh newspapers, contain articles about various events and activities of the GCAC and the GCA. The articles collected feature topics on gardens around Pittsburgh and the Pittsburgh Horticultural and Botanical Societies. Three double-sided scrapbook pages feature items from the GCA's 1961 trip to Hawaii and Japan.
    - GCAC First Meeting Announcement Clipping, 1914 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - GCAC Meeting Announcement Clipping, 1915 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - GCAC Spring Exhibition and GCA Meeting Clippings, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - 9th Annual Dahlia Show Clipping, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Benefit Festival of Pleasant Hill Farm Association Clipping, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Flower Show Clipping, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - "Exhibition of Garden Art" in Carnegie Magazine, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - "Flowers and Gardens in Art" in Carnegie Magazine, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Photos Showing "Garden of a Pompeian Villa" Entry from the Flower and Art Exhibition, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Clippings Related to Mrs. J.G. Pontefract, 1936, 1938, some undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1936 -1958 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Photo of a Knot Garden Exhibited at the New York Flower Show, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Photo of the First Prize Winner at the New York Flower Show, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Crayon Drawings of a GCAC Banquet at the Carnegie Institute's Hall of Architecture, drawn by University of Pittsburgh Art Students, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting Directory, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Garden Club of America Annual Meeting Program Book, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Various Items Belonging to Mrs. J.M. Schoonmaker, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - GCA Annual Meeting Publicity Clippings, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Photo of the GCAC Wayside Stand at Garden Market, 1949 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania Turnpike Brochure, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - The Garden Locator of the Garden Club of America edited by Millicent Ann Gates, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Clippings Documenting Donation by Mr. and Mrs. Roy A. Hunt for Carnegie Tech's Library, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - GCAC Visit to Old Economy Village Clippings, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Disbound Scrapbook Documenting GCAC's YMCA - Resaca Street Project, 1971-1973 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania Information, 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Women's National Farm and Garden Association Yearbook, 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Pictures and Program from the 1975 Zone V Meeting (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - GCA Gateway Clipper Outing Clippings, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Green Elephant Publicity ad Newspaper Clippings, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - News and Press Releases, 1985-1987 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - "1930 Garden Club Pilgrimage to Virginia" Booklet, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Magazines, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity, 1990-1999 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Magazines, 2006-2009 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Publicity, 2000-2009 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photos (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster of "Private Gardens" (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photo of "Paul Sculley, Recipient of the Margaret Douglas Medal" (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photo of "Awards Banquet" (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photo of "Museum Greeter" (Box 59, Folder 10)